我要点咖啡外带  洋娃娃  你也要吗
Would you like some more coffee, baby-doll?
不用了  谢谢
I'm fine. Thanks.
我不能叫你洋娃娃吧
Yeah, see, I can't pull of "baby doll," can I?
对  从那次甜甜嘴事件  我们已经学到教训了
No, I think we learned that from the "sugar lips" incident.
我去点茶来喝
I'm gonna get some tea. Okay.
小亲亲  你好吗
How you doing, pumpkin?
行不通
Nope.
你们俩看起来越来越好了呢
So it looks like it's going really well for you two, huh?
我知道  真的很好  其实我正想要菲比搬来我家
I know. Really well. In fact, I'm gonna ask Phoebe to move in with me.
天啊  你觉得呢
Oh, my God. What do you think?
我觉得这真是太棒了  你什么时候要问她
I think that it's so great. When are you gonna ask her?
今晚  你先别透露啊
Tonight. But don't say anything, okay?
我发誓不说  人格担保
I swear. I promise. I promise.
天啊  我超兴奋的
My God, I'm so excited.
我跟你说  记得不要送她花
All right, listen let me tell you, do not get her flowers. Okay?
因为花谢了  她会哭  还会帮花办葬礼之类的
Because y'know, she cries when they die, and there's the whole funeral
亲爱的  下班后再见  好  再见
I'll see you after work, sweetie. Okay. Bye.
我们应该去看什么电影
So, what movie should we see?
盖瑞要请你搬过去跟他住
Gary's gonna ask you to move in with him.
什么  真的吗  他刚才在吧台上跟我说的
What? Really? He just told me at the counter.
他要我保证不会说出去  但我实在是憋不住了
He made me promise not to tell but I couldn't hold it in any longer.
我不敢相信  对  因为太快了  太快
I can't believe this. Right? Because it's fast. Because it's so fast. It's fast.
别激动  是菲比  又不是你
Relax. It's Phoebe, not you. Oh.
菲比  很厉害  有一套
Good for you, Pheebs. Way to go.
不过真的是很快  对吧  才不是呢
No, but it is fast, isn't it? No.
我是很喜欢他  没错  但我还没有准备好要同居
I like him a lot but I don't think I'm ready.
那你打算怎么办  不知道  兵来将挡
So, what are you gonna do? I don't know. I'll just handle it.
干脆找你去疏通他
I'll ask you to talk to him.
我   为何是我
Me? Why me?
因为给予承诺  你最怕了
Because you are so afraid of commitment.
你去跟他说说  让他也跟你一样怕
You talk to him. Make him scared like you,
让他成为一个  男人
make him a man.
我会去试试   但我不确定会多有用
I'll try, but I'm not sure what good it would do...
因为比起以前  我现在已经很不害怕承诺了
...because I'm less afraid of commitment than I used to be.
真是太甜蜜了
That is so sweet.
还是很怕  但我会处理  没问题
Still terrified. I'll take care of it no problem.
老友记  第五季  第21集  掷球游戏
Friends  S05E21  The One With The Ball
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
罗斯   斯塔顿岛真的是岛吗
Hey, Ross, is, uh, Staten Island really an island?
是啊  所以才叫斯塔顿〝岛〞
Uh-huh. That's why they call it Staten "Island."
我还以为那跟长岛一样
Oh, I thought it was like Long Island.
长岛也是岛
Also an island.
几点了  2点17分
Hey, what time is it? Two seventeen.
你知道吗  我们丢这个球
Wow, you realize we've been throwing this ball
连续一小时都没有漏接落地
without dropping it for an hour?
你说真的
Are you serious?
对  我半小时前就发现了  我怕坏了好事才没说
Yeah, I realized it a half-hour ago, but I didn't wanna say anything because I didn't wanna jinx it.
哇  我们还真会丢接球呢
Wow, we are pretty good at this.
我们完全忘了吃午饭
Hey, we totally forgot about lunch.
这是我第一次忘记吃饭
I think that's the first time I've ever missed a meal.
对  我的裤子都有点松了
Yeah, my pants are a little loose!
嗨  两位  摩妮卡在吗
Hey, you guys. Uh, is Monica here?
不在  不在
No. No.
听着  我带了东西回来  我不确定她会喜欢
All right listen umm, I just bought something I'm not sure she's gonna like it,
听起有点奇怪
And it's gonna seem crazy...
那个东西我从小就想要了
...but this is something I've wanted since I was a little girl.
你带史恩卡希迪来
You bought Shaun Cassidy.
不是  我也希望是
No. I wish.
你们准备好了没   好了
Okay, you ready? Yeah.
那好
OK
请看
Check it out.
那是啥啊  什么鬼东西
Oh, my God. What is it? What the hell is that?
这是猫啊
It's a cat.
这才不是猫
That is not a cat.
这就是猫啊
Yes, it is.
他的皮怎么翻出来了
Why is it inside out?
帮帮忙
Excuse me,
这可是展示级的  纯种狮身人面猫
but this is a purebred, show-quality sphinx cat.
你花了多少钱买的
How much did you pay for that?
有点奢侈  但我谈到了很好的价钱
Well, it was a little extravagant, but I got a pretty good deal.
是吗  多少钱
Yeah, how much?
一千美元
A thousand bucks.
买一只猫
On a cat?
那才不是猫
It's not a cat.
你们这两个玩球的  给我听好了
All right. Listen, ball boys.
我小时候祖母就养了这种猫  他们最讨人喜欢了
My grandmother had one of these when I was little. and it was the sweetest thing.
超可爱的  躺在我的膝盖上  整天满足地喵喵叫
I mean, it was so cute, it would sit in my lap and just purr all day long...
我还会拿鞋带在地上拖  让他追着跑
...and I would drag a shoe string on the ground and it would chase it.
不要钱的猫也会那样啊
Free cats do that too, you know.
那才不是猫
It's not a cat.
反正我买得很兴奋  我才不管你们怎么想
Look, guys, I'm really excited about this, okay? I don't care what you think.
我要去帮威丝克森太太   张罗出一个小猫砂盒
I'm gonna go set up a little litter box for Mrs. Whiskerson.
不然我要叫他〝毛毛〞吗
Well, what am I gonna call her? Fluffy?
你要去吃点东西吗
Hey, do you wanna get something to eat
还是要看我们能来回丢多久
or, uh..do you wanna see how long we can throw this ball back and forth? Huh?
继续丢球  是啊
Uh, the ball thing. Yeah?
罗斯  若我们连丢两小时不落地  那样是不是很棒
Hey, Ross, wouldn't it be great if we could go for like two straight hours without dropping it?
当然啦
Uh, yeah, it would.
来吧  好
Let's do it. Okay.
怎么了
Uh-oh. What?
我要尿尿  但瑞秋在厕所里
I have to pee. And Rachel's in the bathroom.
没想到这样也行
Man, I didn't think we were gonna make it.
是啊
I know.
你别换手喔
Don't switch hands, okay?
小姐们  你们在这里干嘛
Hey, ladies. What are you in here for?
钱德  你来这里干嘛
Hey, Chandler, what are you doing here?
盖瑞  我是来报案的  是吗
Gary, I am here to report a crime. Yeah?
我们俩不常聚在一起  是一种罪
It is a crime that you and I don't spend more time together.
你有什么事
Ha, ha. What's up?
听说你在考虑要菲比跟你同居
Uh, well, I heard that you were thinking about asking Phoebe to move in with you...
我心想我们或许应该聊聊  男人跟我的对话
...and I thought maybe we should have a talk, you know, man to... well, me.
好啊  没问题
Sure, okay.
你在发什么神经
Um, are you crazy?
你疯了  若你和菲比同居  你们两个就会住在一起了
Are you insane? If you live with Phoebe, you two are gonna be, you know, living together.
对  我考虑过了  我知道这会让我快乐
Yeah, I considered that. I just know it'd make me happy.
你是说害怕吧  不  我是说快乐
Heh. You mean scared. No, I mean happy.
害怕  快乐
Scared happy.
钱德  你在干嘛
Chandler, what are you doing?
我在让你张开眼睛啊  你看不出来吗
I am trying to open your eyes, my man! Don't you see,
若你和菲比同居  她就永远都会在
if you lived with Phoebe she's always gonna be there.
你回家会看到她  你上床也会看到她
You're gonna get home, she's there. You go to bed, she's there.
你起床呢  对  她还是在
You wake up and oh, yes, she's there.
我知道  我都等不及了
I know. I can't wait.
你父母的婚姻很幸福  对吧
Were your parents happy or something?
钱德  我看这件事的角度是  我很幸运能找到我的真爱
Listen, Chandler, the way I see it. I was lucky enough to find someone that I really love.
我想要尽量多跟她在一起
I just wanna be around her as much as I can.
怪了  这件事从你嘴里说出来  感觉就没那么恐怖了
Wow, you know, when you say it, it doesn't sound so scary.
所以你懂我的意思吧   对  我想我懂
So you know what I'm talking about? Yeah, I think I do.
这样吧  跟她同居
You know what? You move in with her.
马上  就去跟她同居
You move in right with her right now.
或许我也应该和摩妮卡同居
Maybe I should move in with Monica.
不成  你们不能操之过急
No, it's too soon for you guys.
是啊  你说的对
Yeah, you're right about that.
他们找到中生代乳齿象化石
…now when they found the remains of the Mesozoic mastodon...
却在嘴部发现到  类似古生代两栖类的构造
...they discovered what appeared to be the remains of a Paleozoic amphibian in its jaws.
怎么会牛头不对马嘴
How did it get there?
或许这个游戏应该安静一点
Maybe this should be more of a quiet game.
嗨  嗨
Hey, guys. Hey.
乔伊  我昨晚把手表放在柜子上
Joey, I left my watch on the counter last night.
本来还在这里  到哪儿去了
It was right here, Where is it?
我不知道  别闹了  我上班快迟到了
I don't know. Well, come on, I'm late for work.
你怎么知道  你又没戴表
How do you know? You don't have a watch.
你们能不能停一下再丢球  先帮我找表
Guys, could you stop throwing the ball for one minute and just help me find it?
不知道  没办法喔
Oh, I don't know. Yeah, can't do it.
怎样啦
What?
怎样都好  千万别把球掉地上
Whatever you do, do not drop that ball
我们保持球不落地已经
Yeah, we haven't dropped it in...
2小时27分钟
Two hours, 27 minutes.
真的啊
Really?
我今天没办法去上班  我人不太舒服
I'm not gonna be able to make it in to work today. Um, I don't feel very good.
漂亮
Yes!
我刚才突然觉得自己好多了  但其实没有
Wow, uh, for a second there, I thought I was feeling better, but I'm not.
瑞秋  嗨
Hey, Rach. Hey.
快来看  球不落地接近三小时
Check it out. Almost three hours without dropping it.
恭喜了  真是浪费时间
Wow, congratulations. That's quite a waste of time.
瑞秋  怎么了
Rach. Yeah.
你身上都是抓痕  怎么了
You have scratches all over you. What happened?
是我的猫  什么
Well, it's my cat. What?
对了  我养了只猫  我不想养猫了
Oh, yeah, I got a cat. I don't want a cat.
别担心  那不是猫  没错
Oh, don't worry, it's not a cat. Yeah.
这只猫跟我祖母养过的猫  完全不一样
You guys, this cat is nothing like my grandmother's cat.
既不讨人喜欢  也不可爱
It's not sweet. It's not cute.
我在地上拉着线逗他玩
I even dragged a string on the ground...
他竟然发飙  把我抓得乱七八糟
...and it just flipped out and scratched the hell out of me.
我知道这听来很疯狂  但我发誓
And I swear... I know this sounds crazy,
这只猫每次嘘我的时候  我知道他都在说〝瑞秋〞
but every time this cat hisses at me I know it's saying, "Rachel."
花一千美元买一只猫  比刚才那些话更疯狂
Doesn't sound as crazy as paying $1000 for a cat.
你欠我三百美元不还  还拿一千美元去买猫
You paid $1000 for a cat when you owe me 300?
我本来打算让你跟他玩的
Well, I was gonna let you play with it.
（中央咖啡厅）
嗨
Hey.
你跟盖瑞聊过同居的事没
Hmm, Did you talk to Gary about the moving in thing?
聊过了  我觉得你应该答应
Yes, I did, and I think you should do it.
什么
What?
他很棒  他也很爱你  你非常幸运
He's a great guy, y'know? and he loves you a lot. You are a very lucky lady.
你真没用
You are useless.
害怕承诺是你唯一会做的事
Freaking out about commitment is the one thing you can do...
你竟然连那件事都做不好  天啊
The one thing! And you can't even do that right! God!
抱歉
Sorry.
换做我都愿意和他同居
If he asked me, I'd move in with him.
窝囊废  你滚吧
get out of here, good-for-nothing.
嘿  钱德  嘿  盖瑞
Hey, Chandler. Hey, Gar.
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
能不能先聊下  好啊
Can I talk to you for a second? Yeah. .
好
Okay
你今天很美
You look very pretty today.
谢谢  好吧
Thanks. Okay.
是这样的  好
Here's the thing. Yeah.
我很想让这段关系更进一步
You know, I really want this relationship to move forward.
因为不进则退
Because if you're not moving forward, you know, you're just moving backwards.
不是那样的  真的  如果不进  就是静止不动
Now, that's not true. If you're not moving forward, you're staying still.
静止不动是很好的  你看
And staying still is good. Watch this.
菲比  是
Phoebe? Yeah?
我要你搬来一起住
I want you to move in with me.
那真是太甜蜜了
That is so sweet.
但你不觉得稍微太快了点吗
But don't you think that it's a little it's too soon?
我们彼此  还有很多地方并不太了解
I mean, there's so much we don't know about each other.
好吧  我懂了
Oh, okay. I get it.
我只是  不希望我们操之过急  你懂吧
I just—I don't want us to jump into something that we're not ready for, you know.
我不想搞砸我们现在的一切
I really don't want to mess up what we have.
我担心同居会铸成大错
I'm just—I'm worried it's gonna be a big mistake.
是啊
Yeah.
所以我的答案是  我答应
Which is why my answer is yes.
真的吗
Really? Uh-huh.
你好高兴
Uh-huh! You're so happy.
摩妮卡  别用那么大力气
Monica, stop throwing it so hard.
我们是同一队
We're on the same team.
四个小时  你们就这样丢了四小时
Four hours? You guys have been doing this for four hours?
宝贝  没错
That's right, baby.
好  让我加入  不  不行
All right. Let me in. No, no. Don't do it.
什么
What?
他是漏球大王
He's a dropper.
对  没错
Oh, yeah. That's right.
我才不是漏球大王
I'm not a dropper.
这其实是三个人的游戏
It's really a three-person game, you know?
还不就是你丢我接
It's throwing and catching.
好吧
All right.
喔  好难啊
Oh, oh, it's so hard.
别紧张  那不是猫啊
Don't worry, guys. It's not a cat.
我的  天啊
Oh, my... Oh, good God.
我放弃了  我不知道要怎么处理这玩意儿
I give up, you guys. I don't know what I'm gonna do with this thing.
送他进烤箱也没用
Baking it didn't help, huh?
送回你买的地方呢
Why don't you just take it back to where you got it?
我试过了  他们不收
I tried. They won't take her back.
或许是因为他是反基督的爪牙
Maybe that's because she's a minion of the Antichrist.
瑞秋  店家为什么不收
Rach, why won't they take it back?
他们说要收回可以  但只退我店里的购物券
Well, they said they would, but would only give me store credit.
我用它来买什么呢   一千只普通的猫不成
What am I gonna do, get a thousand regular cats?
不然你先留着  等到你找到处理的方法
If you want, you can keep it until you find out what to do with it.
不行  那不是重点
No, Mon, that's not the point.
我花费一千美元  却搞得全身都是抓痕
I'm out a thousand dollars.I'm all scratched up
还跟长得像手的蠢猫困在一起
and I'm stuck with this stupid cat that looks like a hand.
天啊  那只猫害我流眼泪了
Oh, my God. The cat's made my eyes water.
别给我丢球
Don't throw it to me.
我的视力受损了
My vision's been compromised.
天啊  好了
Oh, God. Okay. Okay.
现在好了  真是惊险
It's okay. Man, that was close.
是啊  你的反应也太大了点
Yeah, you almost overreacted to something.
我们有个好消息  我们要同居了  是不是很棒
We have great news. We're moving in together. Isn't it great?
恭喜  是啊  我好兴奋
Congratulations. That's great.I know, I'm so excited.
我也是
So am I.
你才没有我兴奋  不可能  我是最兴奋的
Well, you're not more excited than I am. No way. I'm the most excited. Ha.
好  晚点在局里见
Okay, I'll see you at the station later.
好  晚点见  别忘了同居的事
Okay, yeah, I'll see you later. Don't forget about the moving-in.
你要搬去跟他住  怎么了
So you're moving in with him? What happened?
我不忍心拒绝他  看他伤心成那样
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad.
或许不会有事的
But maybe it'll be all right.
我真的很喜欢他  同居八成也是迟早的事
I do really like him a lot. and probably do it eventually anyway.
想想也可以省下不少邮票钱
And plus, think of all the money I'll save on stamps.
怎么着  你常写信给他
Why, do you write him a lot?
不是  只是我听说同居的人  会分担邮票的费用  不是吗
No, I just heard when people live together, they split the cost of stamps. Don't they?
是啊  没错
Yeah, yeah. That's right.
抱歉  耐热手套吓了我一跳
Oh, I'm sorry, the oven mitts really freaked me out.
嘿  亲爱的
Hey, honey.
你找到公寓没有  布鲁克林高地有吗
Okay, so did you find any apartments? Anything in Brooklyn Heights?
没有  没找到
No, nothing.
真的  是啊
Oh, really? Yeah.
问都没有  没有
Nothing at all? No.
只要有公寓招租  我们马上搬进去
As soon as something opens up, we'll move right in.
不过要有附泳池的  我需要泳池
Unless it doesn't have a pool. I need a pool.
菲比  可以跟你聊一下吗
Phoebe, can I talk to you for a second? Uh-huh.
请坐  好
Take a seat. Okay.
你没事吧  还好吧
You okay? You feel all right?
我很好啊  因为我们要同居了
Yeah, I feel great because we're moving in together.
报上布鲁克林高地的租屋广告  你都看过了
So you, uh.You checked the paper for listings in Brooklyn Heights, right?
《邮报》你有查过吗
You-you checked the Post?
有查啊  啥都没有
Yeah, uh-huh, there was nothing.
我能喝点水吗   等下
Can I get some water? In a minute.
你查过今天的《邮报》吗
You checked today's Post?
对  我是看今天的
Um, yeah, today's.
这是今天的《邮报》
Hmm. Because, uh, this is today's Post.
我找到了这些租屋广告
And, uh, these are the listings I found.
布鲁克林高地  两房
Brooklyn Heights, two bedrooms.
布鲁克林高地  一房
Brooklyn Heights, one bedroom.
布鲁克林高地区  布鲁克林高地区  布鲁克林高地区
Brooklyn Heights, Brooklyn Heights, Brooklyn Heights.
这些是要租的吗
Oh, are these for rent?
我以为他们是在炫耀自己的房子有多棒
I thought people were just bragging.
我来告诉你  我的想法
Let me tell you what I think might be going on here.
不要看桌子  看着我
No, no, don't look at the table. Look at me.
好吧  一个男生要求一个女生同居
Okay, I think somebody asked someone to move in with him.
女生本来说好  现在反悔了
And I think someone said yes, but now she's having doubts...
因为女生觉得这样太快了
...because things are moving too fast for someone.
你觉得是不是这样
Does that sound at all possible to you?
对  好  我就是那个女生
Yes, yes. Yes, fine, I am someone.
你要我说老实话  对  我是不确定
You want me to say it? I have doubts.
对不起
I'm sorry.
菲比  什么事
Phoebe. Yeah?
菲比  你有这种感觉也没关系
Phoebe, it's okay that you feel this way.
这真的是很快  我们彼此有许多地方不了解
I mean, it is soon, and there's a lot of things we don't know about each other.
我只是觉得  我知道的你  我都很喜欢
I just figured everything I know about you, I really like.
我还不知道的你  就等同居后再慢慢了解
The things I don't know, I get to learn in a place with both our names on the mailbox.
那样好甜蜜啊
That's so sweet.
亲爱的
Sweetheart,
如果你觉得这样太快了  就不行的话
but none of that matters if it's too soon for you.
我们也不用赶着现在就同居  我只要你快乐
It's fine. We don't have to move in together. I just want you to be happy.
跟你同居会让我快乐的
Living with you would make me happy.
菲比  你不用那样说
Phoebe, you don't have to say that.
不  我很想跟你住在一起  我要跟你同居
No, I really wanna live with you. I wanna move in with you.
你确定
Are you sure?
对  百分之百确定
Yes. Definitely, yes.
我们一起住在公寓同居吧
Let's live in an apartment that we both live in.
太好了
Oh, that's great.
等等
Oh, wait, one sec. One sec.
镜子后面的人
Hey, you. Behind the glass.
你看个什么劲啊
Who are you looking at?
我每次进来这种房间  都想说这句话
I've always wanted to say that every time I was in one of these rooms...
虽然我从没进来过
...which was never.
展示猫   高级的展示猫
Show cat. Quality show cat.
展示猫
Show cat. Oh, my God.
天啊  你的宝宝怎么了
What's wrong with your baby?
这不是宝宝  这是猫
That's not a baby. That's a cat.
长得还真吓人
Ew, it's creepy looking. .
不  他其实很讨人喜欢的  不信你看
Oh, no. no, it's actually very sweet. It's very sweet. Look.
你要不要
Yeah. Do you want it?
不了  我恨死猫了
Ha, ha. No, I hate cats.
那你干嘛跟我扯半天  滚吧  继续走你的路
Well, so then what are you doing to me? Okay? Just get out of here, all right? Move on.
帮帮忙
Jeez
这只猫真不寻常
Wow, what an unusual cat.
是的  谢谢你  真的是这样  你要吗
Yes, thank you. Exactly. You want it?
有可能  我考虑要养猫  我正好要去流浪动物之家
Maybe. I was thinking about getting a cat. I was just gonna go to the shelter, but...
好吧  就他了
Okay. Why not?
太好了  总共是两千美元
Oh, terrific. That'll be $2,000.
什么   好吧  一千
Ha. What? Okay, a thousand.
我以为你是要我认养你的猫
I thought you wanted me to adopt your cat?
是啊  不过这不只是猫  更是像是一项投资
Well, I do, but you're gonna have to look at this as more of an investment than a cat.
好吧  我要的只是猫
Okay, yeah. I just wanted a cat.
好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
你显然是杀价高手
Obviously, you know how to haggle...
所以我就不唬弄你了
...so I'm not gonna try and take you on, okay?
算你八百  我也不报警了  因为你这根本是抢劫
So $800, and I don't call the copswhich I should because you are robbing me blind.
把钱留下  猫带走  溜之大吉吧
Blind. Just take the cat, leave the money and run away. Just run away.
可恶
Damn it. Ugh.
死猫  你起码也笑一下嘛
Can't you at least smile or something?
有没有人听到  谁听到了
Okay, did anybody just hear that? Anybody?
我饿死了
I'm starving.
你们振作一点  就快达成连续十小时了
Come on, guys. Suck it up. We're closing in on 10 hours.
这是比毅力的时刻
It's gut-check time.
怎么变成是你当老大  这游戏是我们发明的
I don't know who made you the boss. We invented this game.
帮帮忙  这游戏是因为我  才有现在的局面
Please. I made this game what it is.
不再好玩的局面
Not fun anymore?
我还是很饿
I'm still hungry.
好吧  我家还有一点比萨  你们可以用一手吃吧
All right, there's some pizza at my place. We can eat with one hand, right?
要不要  我要
Are you with me? I am.
好  我们走
All right, let's go. Come on.
摩妮卡大队  走啦
Let's go, Team Monica.
好啦  队名等一下再讨论
All right, we can work out the name later.
瑞秋  你的猫在我碗里干嘛
Rachel, what is your cat doing in one of my bowls?
不是啦  我在解冻鸡肉
It's not. I'm defrosting a chicken.
我把威丝克森太太卖掉了
Oh, I sold, uh, Mrs. Whiskerson.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
你的钱拿回来没
Did you get your money back?
有  一千五百美元
Yeah, $1500.
哇  你还有赚啊
Wow, you made a profit?
我是来拿红丝绒枕头的
I just came for the red velvet pillow.
在这里  瑞秋  谢了
Oh yeah, There you go. Thanks, Rachel.
别忘了  你随时可以来看他
And, uh, don't forget, you can come visit her any time you want.
好  我会记得的
Oh, good. Great. I'll keep that in mind.
这是啥  某种蛇吗
Ahem, hey. So what is this? some kind of snake or something?
我真喜欢和你一起醒来  我也是
I really like waking up with you. I like waking up with you too.
今天早上真美
Oh, it's such a beautiful morning.
我可以在床上待一整天
I could stay here all day.
那样不错
That would be great.
我们可以在床上吃早餐
We could have breakfast in bed.
等等  好
Wait, just a second.
不会吧
Oh, no.
来  摩妮卡  有活力点
All right. Come on, Monica. Look alive. Come on, look alive.
很好  你们都起床了
Oh, good. You're all up.
菲比  现在才早上六点  你怎么没在盖瑞那里
Phoebe, it's six o'clock in the morning. Why aren't you at Gary's?
对  结束了  什么
Oh, yeah. That's over. What?
别这样  盖瑞这么好  有什么问题都能解决的
Come on, Gary's such a great guy. Whatever the problem, you can work it out.
他开枪杀了一只鸟  喔  结束了
He shot a bird. Oh, that is over.
太糟糕了  我很遗憾
I'm sorry. That's terrible.
菲比  你还好吧
Phoebe， Are you okay?
放心  我不会有事的
Yeah, yeah, I'll be all right.
嘿  菲比  接住
Oh, hey, here, Pheebs.
我不太想玩球
Oh. Nah, I don't feel like playing.
没事  没事
It's okay. It's okay.
就当没发生这件事   没必要让别人知道
Just pretend that it didn't happen, okay? No one needs to know.
菲比又不是正式的队员  正式队员漏球才算数
Phoebe's not an official ball player.I mean, only official ball players can drop the ball.
算了  我好饿   走吧
All right. Okay. I'm starving!
菲比  要吃早餐吗
Phoebe, honey, you wanna get breakfast?
好  我们来赛跑  最先到的赢
Yeah. Okay. Okay, let's race. First one there wins. Ha, ha.
你们要在这里吃吗  好啊
You guys wanna eat here? Yeah.
想起来真的很棒吧
Oh, man, that was great, huh?
真不敢相信我们丢了那么久
Can you believe how long we threw that ball around?
是啊  撑了那么久  真的不可思议
Yeah, It is amazing it lasted that long.
是啊  我的手臂酸死了
I know. My arm is killing me.
不是  我是说有漏球高手在  还能撑那么久
No, I meant with the dropper over here.
〝漏球高手〞这称号  怎么会落到我头上
You know, how did I get this reputation as a dropper? Okay?
我再怎么说  也不是漏球高手啊
I am anything but a dropper.
罗斯
Ross.